db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Who has the most wins as a head coach in the NFL?',
	a: 'George Halas',
	b: 'Curly Lambeau',
	c: 'Tom Landry',
	d: 'Don Shula',
	answer: 'Don Shula'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Which NFL team features a helmet decal only on one side of the helmet?',
	a: 'Houston Texans',
	b: 'Jacksonville Jaguars',
	c: 'Pittsburgh Steelers',
	d: 'Tennessee Titans',
	answer: 'Pittsburgh Steelers'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Who is the last non-quarterback to win NFL MVP?',
	a: 'Shaun Alexander',
	b: 'Ray Lewis',
	c: 'Adrian Peterson',
	d: 'LaDainian Tomlinson',
	answer: 'Adrian Peterson'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Which NFL Quarterback, a 2010 Pro Bowler, never started a game at QB in college?',
	a: 'Matt Schaub',
	b: 'Matt Cassel',
	c: 'Matt Moore',
	d: 'Matt Flynn',
	answer: 'Matt Cassel'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: '4 of the first 5 picks in the 1989 draft, Troy Aikman, Barry Sanders, Derrick Thomas, and Deion Sanders, are in the Hall of Fame. Who was the bust?',
	a: 'Aundray Bruce',
	b: 'Blair Thomas',
	c: 'Keith McCants',
	d: 'Tony Mandarich',
	answer: 'Tony Mandarich'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Which of these teams was NOT an original NFL team that moved over to the AFC?',
	a: 'Browns',
	b: 'Colts',
	c: 'Raiders',
	d: 'Steelers',
	answer: 'Raiders'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Who is the only player enshrined in Canton AND in the CFL Hall of Fame?',
	a: 'Fred Biletnikoff',
	b: 'Warren Moon',
	c: 'Joe Theisman',
	d: 'Doug Flutie',
	answer: 'Warren Moon'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'This state has produced more pro football Hall of Famers than any other state',
	a: 'California',
	b: 'Ohio',
	c: 'Pennsylvania',
	d: 'Texas',
	answer: 'Pennsylvania'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Who is the only Super Bowl MVP to have played on the losing team?',
	a: 'Larry Fitzgerald',
	b: 'Chuck Howley',
	c: 'Dan Marino',
	d: 'Steve McNair',
	answer: 'Chuck Howley'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Emmitt Smith is the NFL\'s all-time leading rusher with 18,355 career yards. Who is second?',
	a: 'Eric Dickerson',
	b: 'Curtis Martin',
	c: 'Walter Payton',
	d: 'Barry Sanders',
	answer: 'Walter Payton'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Who holds the single-season record for touchdown receptions with 23?',
	a: 'Randy Moss',
	b: 'Jerry Rice',
	c: 'Calvin Johnson',
	d: 'Terrell Owens',
	answer: 'Randy Moss'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'In the 1985 draft, the 49ers traded picks with this franchise to move up to the 16th slot to select Jerry Rice',
	a: 'Green Bay Packers',
	b: 'Indianapolis Colts',
	c: 'New England Patriots',
	d: 'Seattle Seahawks',
	answer: 'New England Patriots'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Who holds the record for the longest field goal in NFL history?',
	a: 'Tom Dempsey',
	b: 'Matt Prater',
	c: 'Jason Elam',
	d: 'Sebastian Janikowski',
	answer: 'Matt Prater'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Which of these defensive players did not win a Super Bowl MVP?',
	a: 'Richard Dent',
	b: 'Lawrence Taylor',
	c: 'Harvey Martin',
	d: 'Ray Lewis',
	answer: 'Lawrence Taylor'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'CBS paid a record $550,000 fine after this musician had a wardrobe malfunction during the Super Bowl XXXVIII halftime show',
	a: 'Britney Spears',
	b: 'Janet Jackson',
	c: 'Madonna',
	d: 'Tina Turner',
	answer: 'Janet Jackson'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Scott Norwood\'s "Wide Right" miss to end Super Bowl XXV was no chip shot. How long was the attempt?',
	a: '45 yards',
	b: '47 yards',
	c: '49 yards',
	d: '43 yards',
	answer: '47 yards'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'The Seattle Seahawks pay this university a licensing fee to use the "12th Man" slogan',
	a: 'Auburn',
	b: 'Clemson',
	c: 'Texas A&M',
	d: 'Wisconsin',
	answer: 'Texas A&M'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Who is the only member of both the Pro Football Hall of Fame in Canton, Ohio and the Pro Wrestling Hall of Fame in Amsterdam, New York?',
	a: 'Alex Karras',
	b: 'Ernie Ladd',
	c: 'Steve McMichael',
	d: 'Bronko Nagurski',
	answer: 'Bronko Nagurski'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'As defensive coordinator of the 1985 Bears, Buddy Ryan is hailed as the architect of this defensive scheme',
	a: '3-4',
	b: '46',
	c: 'Tampa 2',
	d: 'Zone Blitz',
	answer: '46'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'As MVP of the Super Bowl against the Seahawks, Patriots QB Tom Brady received a Chevrolet truck. To which teammate did he give the keys?',
	a: 'Darrell Revis',
	b: 'Rob Gronkowski',
	c: 'Julian Edelman',
	d: 'Malcolm Butler',
	answer: 'Malcolm Butler'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Peyton Manning\'s playoff winning percentage is...',
	a: '.514',
	b: '.489',
	c: '.458',
	d: '.437',
	answer: '.458'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Which Major League Baseball team selected both John Elway and Dan Marino in the 1979 amateur draft?',
	a: 'New York Yankees',
	b: 'Kansas City Royals',
	c: 'Pittsburgh Pirates',
	d: 'Los Angeles Dodgers',
	answer: 'Kansas City Royals'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Michael Vick was the first quaterback selected in the 2001 draft. Who was second?',
	a: 'Kyle Boller',
	b: 'Drew Brees',
	c: 'Joey Harrington',
	d: 'Byron Leftwich',
	answer: 'Drew Brees'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'What team has the most NFL titles?',
	a: 'Packers',
	b: 'Cowboys',
	c: 'Steelers',
	d: 'Browns',
	answer: 'Packers'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Who has the most passing yards in a single game?',
	a: 'Dan Fouts',
	b: 'Norm Van Brocklin',
	c: 'Peyton Manning',
	d: 'Drew Brees',
	answer: 'Norm Van Brocklin'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'What year was the 1st NFL playoff game?',
	a: '1932',
	b: '1970',
	c: '1920',
	d: '1967',
	answer: '1932'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Who has the most touchdowns in a rookie season?',
	a: 'Barry Sanders',
	b: 'Gayle Sayers',
	c: 'Ezekiel Elliott',
	d: 'Adrian Peterson',
	answer: 'Gayle Sayers'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Who was the 1st Super Bowl MVP?',
	a: 'Paul Hornung',
	b: 'Bart Starr',
	c: 'Max McGee',
	d: 'Vince Lombardi',
	answer: 'Bart Starr'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'Which of these QB\'s was NOT the #1 overall pick in the NFL draft?',
	a: 'Troy Aikman',
	b: 'Johnny Unitas',
	c: 'Terry Bradshaw',
	d: 'Alex Smith',
	answer: 'Johnny Unitas'
});
db.trivia.insert({
	question: 'What pick is the earliest a Kicker or Punter has ever been selected in the NFL draft?',
	a: '6',
	b: '15 ',
	c: '27',
	d: '42',
	answer: '6'
});